So, as you can see, it says, Make Today Real. Check off
your Core 4 domain and a quick win first.
So, you can click on this, and it'll take you straight to
the daily. What the Core 4 is, is for you to track
your daily points every single day inside of the four areas of
life.
that we focus on inside of Standard, which is Core 4. Body,
Being, Balance, and Business. Body's getting your workout in.
Being, doing something like a stack, I mean a flow, or reading
the Bible, or scripture, or whatever. Again, feeds your, your, your normal
need.
And then balance. balance would be, a date night, a text to
your wife or husband, a text to your kid.
And then business is gonna be any takeaway, or anything that you've
learned or did, or strategically made part of your daily habits inside
of business.
What you'll notice here is, on the side, you'll see the logo
start to fill as you create the, the completion of your day.
So it's always going to track your day. It's very simple. It's
very easy to come in here and actually click this, and track
your daily targets every single day.
So that means Saturday we're going to be ready to go. And
then as you can go back, you can see if, if there's
ever a day where you don't fully complete your four, it's going
to show not completed up top.
But again, we're just tracking this from a day-to-day perspective. The overall
target is what? 28 points a week inside of Core 4.
That's seven days a week, four points a day, and you can
get 28 points. Inside of Core 4. If I go back to
Hub, again, I'm just going to continue down this path of what's
going on.